<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="43">
    <author>Wopster</author>
    <version>1.0.1.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Manual Attach</en>
        <de>Manuelles Ankuppeln</de>
        <fr>Attacher manuellement</fr>
        <nl>Handmatig aankoppelen</nl>
        <pl>Ręczne zaczepianie</pl>
        <ru>Ручная сцепка</ru>
        <cz>Manuální připojování</cz>
        <hu>Kézi Csatlakozás</hu>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[This mod enforces you to attach/detach tools and trailers manually.

Attach/Detach implements:
When attaching an implement the script forces the implement to stay at the lowered state. There are some exceptions made for the frontloaders, skidsteers, shovels, telehandlers, combines and hooklift implements. You're still able to attach and detach those implements from the inside of your vehicle. Note: The connection hoses and power take off still requires to be attached manually for those implements. In order to detach the implement needs to be lowered first! Also make sure the power take off and conenction hoses are detached before detaching the implement.

The mod disables disables attaching and detaching from inside the vehicle (expections are mentioned above). Like the mod tile already suggests it’s not possible anymore to do the quick switches between implements.. get out that vehicle for real this time!

Attach/Detach power take off:
Hit Z in order to attach/detach the power take off.

Keep in mind that a tool needs a power take off, otherwise it can't be turned on!

Attach/Detach connection hoses:
Hold Z (for a short amount of time) in order to attach/detach the connection hoses.

Without attached connection hoses the following can occur:
- You won't be able to control hydraulics (e.g. moving parts, folding, use ridge markers etc)
- You won't be able to use the lights.
- You trailer will be on air brakes.

Changelog v1.0.1.0:
- Fixed callstack when vehicle is still in the trigger but deleted/reloaded at the shop or mission.
- Fixed gamepad controls.
- Fixed connection loop while holding down the key for connecting hoses.
- Fixed MP callstack while connecting hoses.
- Tweaked detection handler.
- Added French and Czech translations.
        ]]>
        </en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[Dieser Mod zwingt dich Geräte und Anhänger manuell anzukoppeln.]]>
        </de>
        <fr>
            <![CDATA[Ce mod vous oblige à attacher/détacher manuellement les outils et les remorques.]]>
        </fr>
        <pl>
            <![CDATA[Ten mod zmusza cię do ręcznego zaczepiania/odczepiania przyczep, maszyn i narzędzi. Mamy nadzieję, że będziesz się dobrze z nim bawił!]]>
        </pl>
        <ru>
            <![CDATA[Этот мод вынуждает присоединять/отсоединять оборудование и прицепы только вручную. Мы надеемся вам понравится этот мод.]]>
        </ru>
        <cz>
            <![CDATA[S tímto módem musíte manuálně připojovat a odpojovat vaše nástroje a vlečky.]]>
        </cz>
        <hu>
            <![CDATA[Ezzel a moddal kézzel kell csatlakoztatnod a pótkocsikat és eszközöket.]]>
        </hu>
        <it>
            <![CDATA[Questa mod ti impone di agganciare / sganciare manualmente strumenti e rimorchi.]]>
        </it>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/loader.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <actions>
        <action name="MA_ATTACH_VEHICLE" axisType="HALF"/>
        <action name="MA_ATTACH_PTO_HOSE" axisType="HALF"/>
    </actions>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MA_ATTACH_VEHICLE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_q"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_10"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MA_ATTACH_PTO_HOSE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_z"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_9"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
</modDesc>
