<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">
    <author>Wopster</author>
    <version>2.1.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Manual Attach</en>
        <de>Manuelles Ankuppeln</de>
        <fr>Attelage manuel</fr>
        <nl>Handmatig aankoppelen</nl>
        <pl>Ręczne zaczepianie</pl>
        <ru>Ручная сцепка</ru>
        <cz>Manuální připojování</cz>
        <hu>Kézi Csatlakozás</hu>
        <it>Collegamento Manuale</it>
        <tr>Manuel Bağlantı</tr>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[This mod enforces you to attach/detach tools and trailers manually.

Attach/Detach implements:
When attaching an implement the script forces the implement to stay at it's lowered state. There are some exceptions made for frontloaders, skidsteers, shovels, telehandlers, combines and hooklift implements. You're still able to attach and detach those implements without having to leave your vehicle.
Note: The connection hoses and power take off still require to be attached manually for those implements.*
In order to detach, the implement needs to be lowered first! Also make sure that the power take off and connection hoses are detached before detaching the implement.

The mod disables attaching and detaching from inside the vehicle (exceptions are mentioned above). Like the mod title already suggests it’s not possible anymore to do the quick switches between implements.. get out that vehicle for real this time!

Attach/Detach power take off:
Hit Z in order to attach/detach the power take off.

Keep in mind that a tool needs a power take off, otherwise it can't be turned on!

Attach/Detach connection hoses:
Hold Z (for a short amount of time) in order to attach/detach the connection hoses.

Without attached connection hoses the following can occur:
- You won't be able to control hydraulics (e.g. moving parts, folding, use ridge markers etc)
- You won't be able to use the lights.
- Brakes will be blocked.

Changelog 2.0.0.0:
- FS22 Release
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[Dieser Mod zwingt dich Geräte und Anhänger manuell anzukoppeln.

Anhängen/Abhängen von Anbaugeräten:

Wenn ein Anbaugerät angehangen wird, zwingt das Skript das Anbaugerät im abgesenkten Zustand zu bleiben. Es gibt ein paar Ausnahmen, Frontlader, Kompaktlader, Schaufeln, Telelader, Mähdrescher und Hakenlift Anbaugeräte.
Es ist weiterhin möglich diese Anbaugeräte vom Fahrzeug aus an und abzubauen.
Anmerkung: Die Schläuche und die Zapfwelle müssen trotzdem noch manuell angebaut werden.
Man muss das Anbaugerät erst absenken um es abzuhängen! Bevor du das Anbaugerät abhängst,
sei dir sicher, dass die Schläuche und die Zapfwelle nicht angeschlossen sind.

Der Mod deaktiviert das An-/Abkuppeln vom Fahrzeug aus (Ausnahmen wurden oben erwähnt).
Wie der Modname schon sagt, ist es nun nicht mehr möglich mal eben schnell zwischen den Anbaugeräten zu wechseln...
steig endlich aus!

An-/abbauen der Zapfwelle:

Drücke y um die Zapfwelle an oder abzubauen.
Behalte im Kopf, dass die Zapfwelle angeschlossen sein muss, andernfalls kannst du das Gerät nicht anschalten.

An-/abkuppeln der Verbindungsschläuche:

Halte y (für eine kurze Zeit) gedrückt um die Schläuche an bzw. abzukuppeln.

Ohne angeschlossene Schläuche kann folgendes passieren:
- Du wirst nicht in der Lage sein die Hydraulik zu kontrollieren (z.B. sich bewegende Teile, ein-/ausklappen, Spuranreißer benutzen etc.)
- Du kannst keine Lichter benutzen.
- Blockierte Bremse.

Changelog 2.0.0.0:
- FS22 Release
]]>
        </de>
        <fr>
            <![CDATA[Ce mod vous oblige à atteler/dételer manuellement les outils portés et trainés.

Atteler/dételer les outils :
Lors de l'attelage d'un outil, le script force le relevage à rester baissé.
Il y a quelques exceptions : les chargeurs frontaux, les débardeurs, les pelles, les télescopiques, les moissonneuses-batteuses et les matériels de levage à crochet. Vous pouvez toujours atteler et dételer ces outils depuis la cabine de votre véhicule.
Remarque : Les flexibles hydrauliques et la prise de force doivent quand même être connectés manuellement pour ces outils.
Pour pouvoir dételer les outils portés, il faut d'abord baisser le relevage ! Avant de dételer l'outil, vérifiez également que la prise de force et les flexibles hydrauliques sont déconnectés.

Ce mod désactive la fonction atteler / dételer depuis la cabine du véhicule (sauf exceptions mentionnées ci-dessus).
Comme le suggère le nom de ce mod, il n'est plus possible de passer rapidement d'un outil à l'autre....
Il va falloir sortir du véhicule !

Mettre / Retirer la prise de force :
Appuyez sur la touche A pour mettre / retirer la prise de force.

Gardez à l'esprit qu'un outil a besoin d'une prise de force, sinon il ne peut pas être mis en marche !

Brancher / débrancher les flexibles hydrauliques :
Appuyez sur la touche A et maintenez pour brancher / débrancher les flexibles hydrauliques.

Si les flexibles hydrauliques ne sont pas branchés, les situations suivantes peuvent se produire :
- Vous ne pourrez pas utiliser les fonctions hydrauliques (dépliage/repliage, traceurs, etc.)
- Vous ne pourrez pas allumer les feux de l'outil.
- Vos outils trainés seront freinés (freinage pneumatique).

Changelog 2.0.0.0:
- FS22 Release
]]>
        </fr>
        <pl>
            <![CDATA[Ten mod zmusza cię do ręcznego zaczepiania/odczepiania przyczep, maszyn i narzędzi. Mamy nadzieję, że będziesz się dobrze z nim bawił!]]>
        </pl>
        <ru>
            <![CDATA[Этот мод вынуждает присоединять/отсоединять оборудование и прицепы только вручную. Мы надеемся вам понравится этот мод.]]>
        </ru>
        <cz>
            <![CDATA[S tímto módem musíte manuálně připojovat a odpojovat vaše nástroje a vlečky.]]>
        </cz>
        <hu>
            <![CDATA[Ezzel a moddal kézzel kell csatlakoztatnod a pótkocsikat és eszközöket.]]>
        </hu>
        <it>
            <![CDATA[Questa mod ti impone di collegare/scollegare attrezzi e rimorchi manualmente.

Attacca/stacca attrezzi:
Quando si collega un attrezzo, lo script forza l'attrezzo a rimanere nello stato abbassato. Ci sono alcune eccezioni fatte per caricatori frontali, minipale, pale, sollevatori telescopici, mietitrebbie e attrezzi per scarrabili. Puoi ancora attaccare e staccare quegli attrezzi senza dover lasciare il tuo veicolo.
Nota: i tubi di collegamento e la presa di forza devono ancora essere collegati manualmente per quegli attrezzi.*
Per staccare l'attrezzo deve essere prima abbassato! Assicurarsi inoltre che la presa di forza ei tubi di collegamento siano staccati prima di staccare l'attrezzo.

La mod disabilita il collegamento e il distacco dall'interno del veicolo (le eccezioni sono menzionate sopra).
Come suggerisce già il titolo della mod, non è più possibile fare i rapidi cambi tra gli attrezzi ... questa volta tira fuori quel veicolo per davvero!

Collegare/scollegare la presa di forza:
Premi Z per collegare/scollegare la presa di forza.

Tieni presente che uno strumento ha bisogno di una presa di forza, altrimenti non può essere acceso!

Collegare/scollegare i tubi dei servizi idraulici, luci e/o similari:
Tenere premuto Z (per un breve periodo di tempo) per collegare/scollegare i tubi dei servizi idraulici, luci e/o similari.

Senza aver collegato i tubi dei servizi idraulici, luci e/o similari, si verificano i seguenti problemi:
- Non sarai in grado di controllare l'idraulica (ad esempio parti mobili, piegatura, utilizzo di marcatori di colmo, ecc.)
- Non potrai usare le luci.
- I freni saranno bloccati.

Changelog 2.0.0.0:
- Versione FS22
]]>
        </it>
        <tr>
            <![CDATA[Bu mod, sizi romörk ve alet bağlantılarını el ile yapmak zorunda bırakacaktır.

    Aletleri el ile tak/sök:
    Bir aleti bağladığınızda, kod aleti alçaltılmış durumda başlatır. Ön yükleyiciler, paletli forkliftler, küreyiciler, teleskopik yükleyiciler, biçerler ve sırtlanılabilen romörkler bu moddan etkilenmez. Bu aletleri aracın içinden çıkmadan takmaya devam edebilirsiniz.
    Not: Yukarıdaki aletlerin bağlantı borularını yine de takmanız gerekiyor.*
    Bağlantıyı sökmeden önce aleti alçaltmanız gerekiyor! Aynı zamanda aleti sökmeden önce bağlantı borularını sökmeyi unutmayın.

    Bu mod, aracın içinden yapılan tak/sök işlemlerini devre dışı bırakacaktır (İstisnalar yukarıda belirtildi). Artık aracın dışına çıkmak zorundasınız!

    Güç çıkışlarını takmak veya sökmek için 'Z' tuşuna basın

    Aletlerin çalışmak için güç bağlantısına ihtiyaç duyduğunu unutmayın!

    Bağlantı borularını takmak veya sökmek için kısa bir süre 'Z' tuşuna basılı tutun

    Bağlantı borularını bağlamazsanız alttaki durumlar ile karşılaşabilirsiniz:
    - Aletteki hidrolikleri kullanamazsınız (Örnek olarak, katlanan parçalar)
    - Aletin ışıklarını çalıştıramazsınız
    - Alet frenleri kitlenecektir

    Güncelleme notları: 2.0.0.0:
    - FS22 Çıkış
    ]]>
        </tr>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="i18n/locale"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <actions>
        <action name="MA_ATTACH_VEHICLE" axisType="HALF"/>
        <action name="MA_ATTACH_PTO_HOSE" axisType="HALF"/>
    </actions>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MA_ATTACH_VEHICLE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_q"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_10"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MA_ATTACH_PTO_HOSE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_z"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_9"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
</modDesc>
